<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<locations>
	<loc name="Swarthdale" bg="town">
	A hub of theivery and body odor, Swarthdale is listed in Frodor's
	travel guide as "A place you'd only want to visit if you had family
	there. And maybe not even then."</loc>

	<loc name="Fnord's Tower" bg="ruins">
	Once the seat of power for a dark necromancer, Fnord's tower has
	since become a mediocre Starbucks.</loc>

	<loc name="Vale of Lager" bg="forest">
	The vale of lager is an enchanted forest, filled with surly, unpleasently
	drunken elves. Only worth visiting for the 2-for-1 Dewdrop and
	Jaegermiester shooters.</loc>

	<loc name="Lice Crossing" bg="town">
	Most travellers leave Lice Crossing with a bit more than they bargained
	for. Stay away from the tavern wenches.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Podunk" bg="town">
	A charming hamlet, if by "charming" you mean "depressing rathole".
	</loc>

	<loc name="Boueffdale" bg="town">
	Boueffdale supplies the tasty hamburgers for miles around. And you
	can smell it from miles around, as well.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Fetidville" bg="town">
	Of all the towns in this glorious land, none live up to their
	name quite so well as this little gem.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Strogue" bg="town">
	Not much going for Strogue other than a mediocre college football team. 
	</loc>

	<loc name="Agoronia" bg="town">
	This was a pleasant resort town until an epidemic of zombism caused some 
	rather messy consequences. Customer service, however, seems to have improved.
	</loc>

	<loc name="The Dark Shambles" bg="ruins">
	A local landmark, every since the Barker twins got themselves killed out there.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Meager Dungeon" bg="ruins">
	Lots of rats, very little treasure.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Cthulhu's Nest" bg="ruins">
	Just stay the hell away. Seriously.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Rathaven" bg="town">
	Not the best place to spend the night, but there is plenty to eat at least.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Shallow Hole" bg="ruins">
	A rather uninspired dungeon.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Moria" bg="ruins">
	No, not *THAT* Moria. The other, boring one.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Raistlin's Outhouse" bg="ruins">
	It's pretty much what the name implies.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Mines of Foo" bg="ruins">
	When the ancient dwarves abandoned the mines, the took pretty much
	anything of value.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Mines of Bar" bg="ruins">
	Legend has it that somehow the labyrinthine mines connect with the
	far-away mines of Foo. Care to find out??
	</loc>

	<loc name="Badnamia" bg="ruins">
	I'm really running out of names for things.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Itchy Clearing" bg="forest">
	Nowhere in the land boasts more Orcs or poison Oak.
	</loc>

	<loc name="The Rottwood" bg="forest">
	An ancient and soggy woodland.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Grove of Gold" bg="forest">
	Figuratively, of course. There's nothing really of value here.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Elfmating Pond" bg="forest">
	This scenic lake is popular with sightseers. 
	</loc>

	<loc name="Mirkwood" bg="forest">
	A rather boring woodland filled with angry trees and
	old hippies.
	</loc>

	<loc name="Sherwood Forest" bg="forest">
	You may catch a glimpse of the famous Robin of Hood, who 
	steals from the rich and gives to the tavern.
	</loc>

</locations>
